Joseph Olapagbo

UX/UI DESIGNER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a certified UX/UI designer, I design responsive websites and mobile apps that are easy to use because of the user-centered approach I love to use.

With the UX/UI design knowledge I have and my work experience,
I have a synergy of understanding that can be applied to solve
critical problems by creating solutions based on real research data
rather than just assumptions.

I love to design products that are user-centered because they enhance the overall user experience.

I'm interested in UX/UI design because it serves as an avenue for me to make use of my problem solving potentials.

WORK HISTORY

Upwork Client - Freelance UX/UI Designer

Egypt, Egypt 11/2022 - 11/2022

- Communicated with product manager to translate project requirements and business objectives into polished user interfaces.
- Used wireframes, mock-ups and prototypes to establish user interface design and architecture.
- Drove UI requirements through to implementation, complete with accurate sizing estimates and task breakdowns.

Bakery CEO - UX/UI Designer

Ogun State, Nigeria 05/2022 - 08/2022

- Communicated with product manager to translate project requirements and business objectives into polished user interfaces.
- Devised site maps and mockups for designs based on proven methodologies and end-user feedback.
- Converted abstract ideas and requirements into user personas and storyboards.
- Conducted live user testing of components and functionality to evaluate effectiveness of designs and enhancements.
- Used wireframes, mock-ups and prototypes to establish user interface design and architecture.
- Drove UI requirements through to implementation, complete with accurate sizing estimates and task breakdowns.

Ogun State, Nigeria 110001 +2347014877302 olapagbojoseph@gmail.com

TECHNICAL PROFILE

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- · Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Canva
- Sketch
- Microsoft Office

COMPETENCIES

User Interface (UI) design

User Experience (UX) design

Excellent Communication

Teamwork and Collaboration

Analytical and Critical Thinking

Active Listening

EDUCATION

01/2022 - 12/2024

Olabisi Onabanjo University (OOU)

Ogun State, Nigeria.

Bachelor of Science: Sociology

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified [UX Designer], [Google] - [May 2022 - August 2022]